(Amy:)You are-- with hair
that smells like strawberries.
(Amy:)And we're going to use that
to our advantage.
(Penny:)Wait. What are you
talking about?
(Amy:)By accepting the invitation,
Bernadette becomes
(Amy:)a double agent
inside the enemy camp.
(Amy:)She could ferret out
Priya's tactics,
(Amy:)identify her weaknesses
(Amy:)and feed her false
information, such as:
(Amy:)Leonard's no stranger
to back-alley cockfights.
(Bernadette:)I don't know.
I'm not a very good liar.
(Bernadette:)They kind of whup that
out of you in Catholic school.
(Amy:)Don't worry.
I'll teach you.
(Amy:)I did two years
of Cub Scouts
(Amy:)before they found
out I was a girl.
(Penny:)Okay, I don't
know you people.
(Penny:)I'm just an innocent
woman wondering
(Penny:)if this shoe store will
take my Texaco card.
(Amy:)How do you feel about
concealing a recording device
(Amy:)in the cleavage of
your ample bosom?
(Bernadette:)I don't want anything
in my ample bosom.
(Amy:)Come on, Strawberries.
Take one for the team.
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪